[TONI] Billy…
If you have a problem,
you know you can tell us, right?
Remember, we're your friends too.
[ENRICO] You shouldn't have bothered,
but thank you for this.
- It's okay. Auntie helped me prepare that.
- "Auntie"?
She's the one who takes care
of me and my sister.
And your father?
He's dead.
[PRECIOUS] It's always going to be
like this if you don't talk to him.
You should probably do it.
[BILLY] She chose to side with my father.
She's just really nice.
Well, I'm not.
I'll find a way to drag him
back to prison.
[ABI] That Billy is so greedy!
She already has everything!
I have nothing!
But I'll take all that away from her.
I won't leave her with anything.
[BOWL CLINKS]
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[CUTLERY CLINKING]
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ABI] If Billy thinks I'll let her win…
she's wrong.
I can be like Billy.
[ABI CHUCKLES]
Success.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Where are you going?
- Why are you all dressed up?
- [CHUCKLES]
To my new job, Ma.
Really?
Someone hired you?
Goodness.
Is that true, Bea?
You always say that,
and then the next thing I know,
you've already resigned.
See? [SCOFFS]
You don't stay long in your jobs.
That's why you won't get anywhere.
You should be more like your sister, Abi.
See what I'm talking about?
She's dedicated,
hardworking, and talented.
All right, Ma.
I'll be just like her, okay?
So you can be impressed and proud of me.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Abi, we need to go!
Abi?
So you won't remind me
that it should have been me who died,
and not Abi.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
Attorney, how long does the process take
once I've filed it?
We have the option to request
a temporary protection order.
Usually, it's released within
24 to 72 hours
if they see an immediate threat.
Even if the hearing is not over,
legally, he's prohibited from approaching.
Yes.
Once there's a TPO, close proximity,
as well as direct
and indirect contact, is prohibited.
Especially if we can prove that
there's an immediate threat.
Thank you, Attorney.
By the way, I sent you some files
about his cases in Canada.
Please check if we can find any loopholes.
Just in case he won't stop.
Thank you, Attorney.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Chief?
Ms. Lindsay is here.
Okay. I'm ready.
I'm sorry it took so long, ma'am.
Ah.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
All good.
All right. I'll just submit this
to the admin.
Excuse me.
[SIGHS]
[OLIVER] That's near where I live.
Just about a three-minute walk.
- See?
- Wow.
I'll become this handsome, see?
All right, I'll get going.
- Okay. Bye!
- Bye!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
If you do this again,
I will file a restraining order.
I don't want any trouble,
but if you drag me into this,
my company, and especially Oliver,
I'll find a way
to have your case in Canada reopened.
[OLIVER] Sir Eric!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [OLIVER] Hello.
- [ENRICO] Hey.
What's up?
We haven't seen each other
all day, Sir Eric!
- Look!
- What's this?
What?
You know how to box?
Oh no, sir!
I'm just training.
Sir Eric.
Do you think that'll help me
when I apply to
the University of Kingsley?
They might think I'm a war freak.
Of course this will help!
Remember this, okay?
Boxing teaches discipline and resilience.
This will look good on your profile!
They'll see that you are
a well-rounded person.
And I'm pretty sure
you'll get that scholarship.
But, of course, you'll be far away.
Will you be okay with the cold climate?
Are you used to being alone?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, what's wrong?
I will feel sad if I leave my sister.
But I just have to endure it.
When I graduate
from the University of Kingsley,
I will work hard to find a job
so my sister can finally rest.
Ever since I was a baby,
she's been working so hard
to provide for me.
So now, it's my turn to make it up to her.
I'll be the one to help her.
So she can finally relax,
and so she won't have to worry about us!
It's my turn to worry about that.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OLIVER] Oh!
Sir Eric, my bus is here!
Bye!
[RESOLUTE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hi, miss.
[RECEPTIONIST] You're here for?
Uh, I'm here for Ms. Camille Cordova.
- Can I get your name?
- Hmm?
[RECEPTIONIST] Name.
Ah, it's Abi.
[RECEPTIONIST] Okay. Abi, Abi, Abi…
Miss, I'm really sorry!
I really need to talk to Ms. Camille!
- Miss, you can't go there!
- Ms. Camille!
- Uh, where's the boardroom?
- Over there.
There? Okay.
Okay. So this will be a sure hit
with the commitment culture these days.
Matching shirts that signify
matches on Pebblng.
It's like wearing a badge in real life.
Match made, verified, and validated.
- [DRAMATIC YAWNING]
- [PAPERS RUSTLE]
Boring!
Can't you think
of something bigger, Morrie?
LoveList already has
LoveSpeak and LoveLine.
We have to be a hundred steps ahead.
We already came up with
the Heart Reward System, right?
And you'll follow that with this?
Couple's shirts? Really?
Well, as well as the couple shirts,
we'll also have a couple watch,
and maybe a couple phone--
Ms. Camille! I need to talk to you.
And you are?
Abi Mercado.
Uh, I have an idea for Pebblng.
- If you'll just listen to me,
- I'm sorry!
- I have a really great--
- I'm sorry, ma'am!
I tried my best to stop her.
Five minutes!
Hold on! Please, just five minutes.
We're in the middle
of a meeting right now.
Exactly. This is a really great idea.
I'm sure you'll be steps ahead
of LoveList!
Miss, if you don't come with me,
I'll call security!
- I'm really sorry--
- Wait.
She said wait.
When a couple meets on LoveList
and reaches marriage,
we celebrate it
as the ultimate validation
of our platform.
- [PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Because in the dating world,
commitment is the real measure of success.
So turning meaningful connections
into lifelong commitments.
That's what we want to achieve
with our latest feature.
LoveFeast.
Turning meaningful connections
into lifelong commitments.
That's the goal for this feature.
[BILLY] Together with our brand partners,
we'll curate sponsored wedding packages
for LoveList couples
who successfully matched,
made it official,
and chose to get married.
So LoveFeast will sponsor
the wedding reception?
[BILLY] Yes, part of it.
But it's bigger than that.
From prenup videos to wedding gowns,
and even the wedding giveaways.
So we'd like to call it LoveFeast,
because it's not just a single giveaway.
It's a spread of experiences.
We're talking about an entire package.
From the prenup video,
wedding gown,
wedding souvenirs,
and much more.
Why is it called LoveFeast?
It'll be a feast of freebies.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
Imagine the hype.
I mean, just in prenup videos alone,
we could rake in millions of views.
And hello, monetization! [CHUCKLES]
There's guaranteed visibility
and long-term brand association
anchored to one of
the most important milestones
in a person's life.
And you're the first one
to hear about this.
I'm in, Billy.
You girls have a deal.
[GASPS, EXCLAIMS]
We have actually prepared
the draft agreement for you, Ms. Lindsay.
We can walk you through it anytime. Here.
You sure don't waste time, do you?
I don't. [GIGGLES]
Okay, I'll go over this.
I'll read it here.
I'm going to send a copy to my lawyer.
And if everything is good,
we can sign before lunch.
Go. No rush, Ms. Lindsay.
Take all the time you need.
Well done.
Uh…
Abi. Abigail Mercado, ma'am.
I mean Ms. Camille.
Well done, Abi.
I need someone like you here at Pebblng.
And you, Morrie.
Post this on our social media pages.
Oh, yes, Ms. Camille. I'll make a draft.
Right now.
Yes, you should do it now.
LoveList might get ahead of us.
That can't happen.
Competitive.
I like that.
[MUSIC FADES]
Blaire, have you checked
Ms. Lindsay's client file?
Are you sure no food allergies?
Yes, chief. A hundred percent sure.
I actually did a taste test
on all of that.
I just made sure it's safe.
I'll have her leftovers.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- You're crazy.
Oh.
Someone's ringing my phone.
Chief,
she's on her way up.
Okay.
Just stand by in case she needs something.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Ms. Lindsay!
Hi, Ms. Lindsay!
We had food brought in for you. Dig in.
- Dig in.
- If you have any food request,
just let us know.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Feel free.
[BILLY CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Billy, where did you get
the concept of LoveFeast?
It was actually inspired
by a wedding proposal.
From here?
[FEMALE VO] You found love at Pebblng.
And now, we're celebrating it!
In our new feature,
we will sponsor the wedding
of couples who matched on Pebblng,
turning swipes into "I do's"!
Because all love stories
deserve a happy ending.
You can forget about the contract.
I'm not signing.
You know, I was prepared
to invest on LoveFeast.
I really love the concept.
But, apparently, it's a replica
of an existing concept.
That's a serious matter, Billy!
My name is built on integrity,
and I plan to protect that.
Yeah, I understand, Ms. Lindsay,
but I can assure you
that LoveFeast is our original idea.
Let me look into it immediately.
Don't waste your time.
You already wasted mine.
[LINE RINGS]
Bea. Bea, why aren't you answering?!
- Bea? Bea!
- [LINE RINGS]
- [LINE DISCONNECTS]
- Argh!
She might leave me too.
Abi, you already left me.
Your father left me as well.
[CRIES]
[SNIFFLES]
Bea…
You cannot leave me.
You can't.
[PICTURE FRAME THUDS]
[BAG THUDS]
I will find you.
I will figure out what you're hiding.
- [SCREAMING]
- [BAG THUDS]
[GRUNTS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
An exact copy.
Could this also have been
Shirley De Leon's work?
I mean, she was once Caloy's boss.
This is clearly an inside job.
We're the only ones
who know about LoveFeast.
How would Shirley know
if she isn't even here?
True.
Then, the one that leaked LoveFeast
must be among us.
[VALERIE SCOFFS]
Wow, I can't believe this.
After everything I did for this company,
you dare accuse me?
- Who else?
- Enough!
This will not solve anything.
Tell me. What would I gain
if I leaked LoveFeast to the competition?
What? You guys still think this
is about Jordan, huh?
FYI, I have a new boyfriend,
and I'm so over Jordan!
We're just friends, okay?
[BLAIRE] Exactly!
Plus one there, girl!
My twin has found herself a new boyfriend!
You should watch her vlogs.
They've already gone full hard launch.
So, who leaked it?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
There's only one way to find out.
Excuse me.
[BIRDS CHIRPING IN DISTANCE]
We really don't know any Bea, ma'am.
Look, she's my daughter.
I saw this among her things.
She works here.
Uh, there's no Bea working here.
You might want to call her first.
She's not even picking up my calls.
I'm sorry.
No Bea is employed here.
Don't tell me she said
she doesn't want to talk to me.
Sorry?
Just admit it!
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
She's hiding from me, isn't she?
She's not planning on coming back?
She's never coming home?
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
- Bea!
- [PRECIOUS] Uh…
Bea?
Bea, sweetheart, come out!
Bea!
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Ma'am…
- Where's my daughter?
- Show her…
- Calm down.
- Bea!
- Take it easy.
- Guard!
- Let me.
- [SCREAMING]
- Oh my…
- I'll take it from here.
- Argh! Don't touch me!
Please take a seat.
- Go ahead, sit down.
- Bea!
Sweetheart!
So, you're saying somebody
leaked the concept?
I don't even know what happened.
Who do you think it is?
The girls think
it's either Shirley or Val,
but my gut tells me that
it's neither of them.
We can't just keep guessing.
I'm on my way to Pebblng.
Pebblng? Your batchmate's company?
Yes.
Their CEO is Camille Cordova.
She can't do to me again
what she did before.
What did she do to you?
Honestly, Ms. Camille,
I've been wanting to
join your company for a long time.
Unfortunately, you weren't hiring.
So today, I just went for it.
And you're exactly what I want.
Someone who is brave,
and someone who finally
thinks outside the box.
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BILLY] We were academic rivals.
I was summa, she was magna cum laude.
A day before the thesis topic proposal,
I found out that we had the same idea.
It turned out, she had learned that
I had done initial research
about coping mechanisms
among women trauma survivors.
She stole my idea.
Damn. So she wasn't just smart in school.
She was also a thief.
Why didn't I know this?
Nah, dude. You were busy at the time,
so I chose not to bother you.
Well…
Who could have leaked
LoveFeast to Camille?
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
Thank you for letting me rent
your apartment.
You're welcome.
You're a hardworking man, Eric.
The previous tenant just left.
It's perfect timing.
Wait here.
I'll just open the gate.
- [HANDLE CLANKING]
- [GATE RATTLING]
Come in.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
Everyone I love…
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
They leave and never return.
My daughter Bea?
I know she wants to leave me.
I understand you.
I was abandoned by my father.
And again
by the man I loved.
The man I was going to marry.
So I know how you feel.
I feel like
Bea won't come back to me.
She'll leave me.
You know, not all of our fears come true.
That's why we must not give in to fear.
You did say
she left for work.
You also said she takes care of you.
That's why I'm sure
that she loves you.
Really?
All of us at Angels of Grace
are here for you.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STAFF] Yes, ma'am?
I'm here for Camille.
- Please tell her it's Billy.
- Uh, Billy…
Um, you don't have an appointment.
Just tell her it's Billy.
- Uh--
- I'm sure she knows me.
- Okay, I'll double--
- Call her now.
All right.
[LINE RINGS]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[ABI] Thank you, Ms. Camille,
for liking my concept.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [RAIN] You're not jealous anymore.
- We're done.
I would do anything for my mother.
That's why I played with fire.
Billy went through a lot because of her.
She'll get through it.
- [ROBBIE] 'Cause you're there for her.
- [JORDAN] She's always there for me too.
[ROBBIE] Ride or die, right?
Billy! What are you doing here?
How did you get your hands
on our LoveFeast concept?
Your concept?
Don't take what's mine!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [BOTH GRUNT]